bizwiki.com 2010-06-24

# Bizwiki | Privacy Policy

This privacy policy sets out how Bizwiki uses and protects any personal information that you submit to Bizwiki when you contact us, create an account or update your My Bizwiki profile.

Bizwiki is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. When you register for a Bizwiki account or update your My Bizwiki profile we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website. You can be assured that this information will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.

Bizwiki may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from Dec 1, 2008.

What we collect

We may collect the following personal information:

  * a username which you select
  * contact information including email address
  * demographic information such as zip code, preferences and interests
  * other information relevant to personalizing your search results and community involvement on Bizwiki

What we do with the information we collect

We primarily collect this information to enable you to securely login to your My Bizwiki account in order to contribute to Bizwiki. Some of the information you choose to give us will be visible to other Bizwiki users such as your username.

Your email address will not be displayed publicly. It is used by Bizwiki in case you forget your password, and to send you information from Bizwiki that you have signed up to receive or may be interested in.

Other possible uses of the information include:

  * Internal record keeping. 
  * We may use the information to improve our products and services. 
  * We may periodically send promotional email about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided. 
  * From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. 
  * We may use the information to customize the website according to your interests.

Security

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. 

How we use cookies

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyze web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences. 

We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyze data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system. 

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. 

You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

Links to other websites

The Bizwiki website contains links to other websites. We do not have any control over the websites. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

Controlling your personal information

You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:

  * Registering for an account on Bizwiki requires you to give us your email address and select a username. If you do not wish to give us this information you are free to remain a public, unregistered user of the website. 
  * If you are registered with Bizwiki you can login at any time to change your personal profile, restricting how much information you provide (other than your username and email address which are required for a Bizwiki account).
  * If you have a Bizwiki account and no longer wish to be registered you can close your account by simply emailing [admin@bizwiki.com](mailto:admin@bizwiki.com).

We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.

You can see what information we hold about you by visiting your My Bizwiki page. 

If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please email us as soon as possible. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.
